Guide to the Edward A. Feigenbaum Papers SC0340
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2005-101
  - Artificial Intelligence and Expert Systems
    - Kay side 5 and 6, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - C650 Progress in Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Legal reasoning, 1992; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - D724 Keynote Address: Artificial Intelligence (AI) as an Experimental Science by Herbert Simon--AAAI National Conference, 1993; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - IQ-17 Presidential Address: Toward an Theory of Knowledge, Reddy AAAI (1/2), 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - IQ-17 Reddy AAAI (2/2), 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - IQ-22 Where are We Now and Where are We Going? (1/2), undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - IQ-22 Where are We Now and Where are We Going? (2/2), undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - IQ-9 Exploiting Task Structure to Automate Knowledge Acquisition, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - KASE, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Future of Computing: Engelbart Symposium, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - DEMETER, Carnagie Mellon CS Dept., undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - View from the Bridge: Highlights from A Senior Software Program Managers Roundtable, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Honda ROBO!! on TV, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Minerva: the Interactive Robotic Tour-Guide, Carnagie Mellon University and the University of Bonn, 1998; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - INCO Expert System NASA Johnson S.C., undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Real World Applications of Causal-Network Diagnostics, 1996; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Steps in Building Expert Systems--Identify, Scope, Maintain, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Diagnosis Expert System for the Automatic Transmission "C3" - Cooperation Ford-Europe / GMD, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Comdex '98-Xerox Keynote, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - 95-96 NIST Colloquium Series, "Can Corporate Research Survive?", by John Seeley Brown, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Artificial Intelligence (AI) n Mfg. Part 3 of 3 - Cutkosky, 1991; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Artificial Intelligence (AI) in Mfg. Part 1 and 2 of 3 - Cutkosky, 1991; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - The Age of Intelligent Machines, by Raymond Kurzweil, 1987; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Kurzweil interview with David Gergen, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Giving Machines Some Thought, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Giving Machines Some Thought, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - StarTeam Award--Ed Feigenbaum, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 31)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1995; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 73, Folder 31.1)
    - 1999 Morris F. Collen Award Presented to Dr. Joshua Lederberg, 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Knowledge-based Expert Systems: Planning and Inplimentation - Randall Davis, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - Expert Systems, Grand Finale, Brighton England--EAF, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1988; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 73, Folder 35.1)
    - Genetic Programming, the Movie, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Speech Recognition 2010: A Look into the Future by William Meisel, 1998; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Brain Actuated Control--GMA, PBS, CNN, 1993--1994; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Genetic Programming 3 Video Sampler: Human Competitive Machine Intelligence, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Expert Systems Take-off: The Airline Seat Advisor--Gail Ward and Michael Biel, 1985; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1985; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 74, Folder 9.1)
    - "Horizon" BBC TV, 1984; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Feigenbaum, MacNeil -Lehrer Report, "Artificial Intelligence", 1987; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - JWID Executive Overview, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - DEC AI The Continuity of Experience "IHI", 1987; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Tape 1: James Burke, Murray Gell-Mann, ACM97: The Next 50 Years of Computing, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Tape 2: Joel Birnbaum, Pattie Maes, Nathan Myhrvold, ACM97: The Next 50 Years of Computing, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Tape 4: Vint Cerf, Brenda Laurel, Maurice Wilkes, ACM97: The Next 50 Years of Computing, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Tape 5: Elliot Soloway, Reed Hundt, Bruce Sterling, ACM97: The Next 50 Years of Computing, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Tape 6: Ray Reddy, Murray Gell-Mann, James Burke, ACM97: The Next 50 Years of Computing, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Packaging Advisor, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Lumiere Demonstration, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Knowledge Navigator, Apple Computer, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - UK IT Panel Meeting: Edison House (EUARD), 1995; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Aaron, H. Cohen, Allen Alda, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium IV: Reel 1 and 2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium IV: Reel 3 and 4 and 5 (East Coast Q and A, Roundtable), 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium III: Natural Language--Tape 1, 1987; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium III: An AI Productivity Roundtable, East Coast Q and A--Tape 2, 1987; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium III: An AI Productivity Roundtable, Segment 1 (Dub from VHS), 1987; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium II: Tape 1, 1986; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium II: Tape 2A, 1986; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium II: Tape 2B, 1986; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Applications Q and A East Coast, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Applications Reels Part 1 and 2, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Feigenbaum Lecture and Q and A, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, undated; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 76, Folder 19.1)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Fox Lecture and Q and A, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Applications with Intros by Harry Tenant, 1985; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Applications Q and A West Coast, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Buchanan Lecture and Q and A, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 23)
      - Use copy, undated; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 76, Folder 23.1)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Reel Q and A - West Coast, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Reel Q and A - East Coast, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - TI Artificial Intelligence (AI) Satellite Symposium: Davis Lecture and Q and A, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - National Defense University--Information Resources Management College--Certificate of Appreciation presented to EAF, 1990 (Box 80)
  - Companies
    - Intellicorp, 1986--1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Intelligenetics, 1989--1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Sperry, 1985--1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - "Heap" #19--Intellicorp Misc., undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Sperry Board--NY, NY--EMPTY, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Sperry--NY, NY--EMPTY, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Sperry, NYC -- EMPTY, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Sperry, NYC--EMPTY, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Sperry, New York --EMPTY, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Sperry, NYC --EMPTY, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Sperry TAB/TAG--Phoenix Arizona, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Sperry Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Sperry Announcement, Washington D.C., 1985 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Sperry/ Rockwell, Burbank, CA, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI) Seminar, Austin TX, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI)Seminar, Washington, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Sperry,NYC, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - HPP Visitors--Short / Sperry, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - Sperry Visitors, Drs. Gerber and Short, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 56)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI) Seminar, Los Angeles EMPTY, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Sperry Board, NYC, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI) /TEK Cambridge, Mass, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Sperry, NYC, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI) / TEK, Washington, D.C., 1984 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Sperry, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Sperry Board, NYC, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Sperry Board, Philadelphia, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Sperry TAB, Long Island, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Sperry, NYC, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI) Seminar, Boston (Cancelled), 1984 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Sperry Board, NYC, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Sperry, NYC, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Sperry, Oakland, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Sperry, NYC, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 76)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI), Palo Alto, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 77)
    - Sperry, New York, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 86)
    - Sperry, New Jersey, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Sperry, Reston, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 68)
    - Stock Announcement, Intelligenetics, 1983 (Box 50A, Folder 11)
    - Executive Briefing Materials, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Teknowledge--Continuing Education Institute (CEI) Briefing, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Executive Briefing Transparencies, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Knowledge Server Talk, undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Teknowledge--Continuing Education Institute (CEI) new and extra transparencies, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Sperry Seminars, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Butler-Cox Talk--Intellicorp Sales Meeting, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Intelligenetics, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - International Advisory Board, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Sperry / SEC, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Sperry--People, 1983--1984 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - General History and Functions of Sperry, 1967--1983 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Sperry--Knowledge Systems Center, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Technical Advisory Board, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Advanced Computer Technology Press Symposium Binder, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Sperry FY '86-'90 Strategic Plan Presentation Binder, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Sperry Reports, Misc., 1984--1989 (Box 61A, Folder 9)
    - Sperry Nominating Committee, 1984 (Box 61A, Folder 10)
    - Sperry Board--SEC Filings, 1983 (Box 61A, Folder 11)
    - Sperry Board, 1983 (Box 61A, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Misc. Correspondence, 1983 (Box 61A, Folder 13)
    - Sperry--Burroughs, 1985--1986 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Sperry Audit Committee Reports 1/2, 1983--1984 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Sperry Audit Committee Reports 2/2, 1983--1984 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Financial reports to Board of Directors 1/3, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Financial reports to Board of Directors 2/3, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Financial reports to Board of Directors 3/3, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Sperry Annual Reports, 1981--1982 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - 10--Q, 1982--1984 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting of Stockholders, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Sperry Board Agenda/Minutes, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Sperry Board Agenda/Minutes, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Sperry Board Agenda/Minutes, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Strategic plan Presentation Binder, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Sperry Corporate Technology Center (CTC) and Artificial Intelligence (AI) Materials, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Sperry Corporate Technology Center (CTC) and Artificial Intelligence (AI) Materials, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Sperry Corporate Technology Center (CTC) and Artificial Intelligence (AI) Materials, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Sperry--Minutes of "Crisis" Meetings, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Intelligenetics emails, 1980--1985 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Intelligenetics--Computational Tools for Molecular Genetics - Binder, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Intelligenetics Stcok Prospectus and Lucite Paperweight, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Letter from Steven Brandt, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Intelligenetics 5 year plan, 1989--1993 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Intelligenetics calls for capitol, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Intelligenetics Historic Docs, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - A Survey of Computer use by Molecular Biologists - Intelligenetics, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Genetic Engineering Workstation (PEPPER Project) External Requirements Review, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Intelligenetics: OTL correspondence and drafts--Intelligenetics legal and response 1/2, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Intelligenetics: OTL correspondence and drafts--Intelligenetics legal and response 2/2, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Intelligenetics--NSF Waiver, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Short License--Intelligenetics, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Business Plan- Intelligenetics, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Hollander--Intelligenetics, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Software Policy Memos, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Meeting Minutes--Intelligenetics, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Intelligenetics Misc., 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Recruiting--Intelligenetics, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - IPO Documents, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Intelligenetics Stock Laws and Filings, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Intelligenetics / Teknowledge Conflict of Interest, 1982--1984 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Intelligenetics Board, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Intelligenetics Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Intelligenetics Board, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Intelligenetics Venture Sale to LePercy, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Potential Customer Letters, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Intelligenetics / DENDRAL, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Intelligenetics Business Plan / Financials, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Intelligenetics Board, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Intelligenetics Business Plan, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Q and A for International Joint Committee on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI) Conference, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors, Annual Reports etc..., 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - KLUE Brochure (The Knowledge Legacy of the Unavailable Expert), 1989 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Intellicorp, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Intellicorp Historical, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Intellicorp, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Intellicorp, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - For Intellicorp--to do, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Intellicorp, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Intellicorp Binder, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Intellicorp Finances, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Intellicorp Products, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - "The Pigeon" Intellicorp's Internal Newsletter, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence--Robert Flast, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Infopacket for Board and Shareholders meeting, 198 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - OpComm Agendas, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Intellicorp, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Intellicorp, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Intellicorp Historical Docs--Balance Sheets and Sales, 1982--1983 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Intellicorp, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Expert Systems (ES) Tutorials--attendees, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Intellicorp Turnaround, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Intellicorp Stock Lucite Prospectus Trophy, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - T.1 User's Guide--Teknowledge, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Teknowledge E-mails, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence re: Expert Systems (ES) for oil industry (France?), 1981 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - "AI: The New Wave" Tutorial by Fred Hayes-Roth, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Teknowledge Consulting Agreements--Earlier Drafts, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Teknowledge Business Plan, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Teknowledge Travle Misc. Bills / Reciepts, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Teknowledge--Conflict of Interest Issue, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Teknowledge / honeywell, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Teknowledge / TRW Proposal, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Teknowledge / G.E., 1982 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Teknowledge / Nixdorf, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Lee Hecht, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Teknowledge: Founding documents, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Teknowledge--Informative Booklet, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Teknowledge History, 1980--1984 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Teknowledge Educational Services, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Teknowledge Executive Briefing Materials, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Teknowledge Briefing Materials, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Teknowledge Executive Briefing, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI): EAF on Expert Systems (ES) with Teknowledge, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Continuing Education Institute (CEI) / Teknowledge Course / Roster, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Teknowledge: Initial Stock Purchases--Shareholder Agreement, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Teknowledge / Purchase of 25k Additional Shares with note, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Teknowledge: Bonus Stocks, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Teknowledge IPO, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Teknowledge / Cimflex Merger, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Teknowledge annual reports, 1988--1989 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Teknowledge Misc., 1982--1983 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Teknowledge Misc., 1981--1983 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Teknowledge Board, 1981--1982 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Teknowledge Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Teknowledge Incorporation, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Teknowledge Business Plan, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Design Power--Design Engineering Information Systems Inc. Business Plan, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - DPI and Alhstrom, CGI, Hawk Holdings, Intellicorp, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Design Power Inc. Business Plans and Materials 1/2, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Design Power Inc. Business Plans and Materials 2/2, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Design Power Inc. and SITRA communications 1/2, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Design Power Inc. and SITRA communications 2/2, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Design Power Inc. and Japan (CSK and ALDN), 1990 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Design Power Inc. Board Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Design Power Inc. Action Folder, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Design Power Inc. Notes / Communications / Reports 1/3, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Design Power Inc. Notes / Communications / Reports 2/3, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Design Power Inc. Notes / Communications / Reports 3/3, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - EAF's Business Cards / Day Planner, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Knowledge Engineering: PAL Format (Sperry), 1985; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Freedom in Flight (Sperry), 1986; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Feigenbaum Intro to Teknowledge Tape, 1984; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1984; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 73, Folder 26.1)
    - Design Power, Inc., undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Intellicorp: Two Weeks: Rapid prototyping at Babcock and Wilcox, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Intellicorp: Pushing the Limit--Knowledge systems at Northrop Aircraft, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Intellicorp: Allen-Bradley and SRI International: Taking control of Systems Complexity, 1987; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Intellicorp: KLUE, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Intellicorp: User group--3M--Marty kenner, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Intellicorp: Expert Systems Take-off Version "D", 1986; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Intellicorp: Expert Systems Take-off Version "D", 1986; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Intellicorp: Expert Systems take-off Version "S", 1986; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - The Science and Technology of Knowledge Engineering - Teknowledge, 1984; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Management Overview--Teknowledge, 1984; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 28)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1984; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 76, Folder 28.1)
    - A Retrospective Sampler of Knowledge Systems--Teknowledge, 1984; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Knowledge Engineering Methodology--Teknowledge, 1984; 1 videotape(s) (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Teknowledge Binder "working notes", 1981 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Papers, articles and correspondence
    - Stories of AAAI--Before the Beginning and After: A Love Letter, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Published books
    - Fifth Generation Book--general, 1982--1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Fifth Generation Publicity, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Fifth Generation--Misc., 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Rise of the Expert Company--John Brockman, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Rise of the Expert Company--Times, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Rise of the Expert Company--Book Working Materials for catalog of existing systems, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Rise of Expert Company--Slide Set, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Rise of the Expert Company Publicity, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Rise of the Expert Company Fan Mail, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Rise of the Expert Company: Tom Peters' forward, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Rise of the Expert Company Revisions, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Rise of the Expert Company Harmon, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Rise of the Expert Company--Complimentary Copies, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Rise of the Expert Company--London, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Rise of the Expert Company--Reviews, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Expert System Book--EAF's Book, with Pam McCorduck, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Fifth Gen Book Reviews and Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - "Heap" #15--Spanish Language Reviews of Fifth Gen, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "Rise of Expert Company" talk (EAF's Talks), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - EAF's Outline of presentation of work reported in "Rise of Expert Company", 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - EAF--Fifth Generation Book Reviews, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Journalists, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Fifth Generation Book, Promotional, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Addisn-Wesley Fifth Generation Book, Packet, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 4)